https://www.alivenetwork.com/2010_adv_privacypolicy.asp

The easy way to hire live bands and entertainers for weddings, corporate events and private parties
01782 740839 Opening hours 9am-5.30pm, Mon-Fri
Find an artist for your event...
Entertainment
Your entertainment type...Rock and Pop Function BandsWedding BandsTribute BandsSoul, RnB & Motown Bands70's Bands, Funk Bands & Disco BandsAcoustic BandsSolo Singers, Music Duos & TriosParty BandsCover BandsChristmas BandsSinger GuitaristsSolo Singers With TracksRat Pack & Swing TributesWedding SingersSaxophone PlayersPianistsHarp MusiciansElectric ViolinistsWedding GuitaristsClassical GuitaristsJazz BandsSwing Jive Rock n Roll BandsBig Bands and Jazz OrchestrasRat Pack & Swing TributesSaxophone PlayersBrass BandsString QuartetsHarp MusiciansClassical GuitaristsPianistsClassical & Opera SingersClassical MusiciansWedding Ceremony MusiciansElectric ViolinistsGospel ChoirsAcapella groupsClassical & Opera SingersCarol SingersSinging WaitersCeilidh BandsTraditional Irish / Folk BandsLatin Bands, Salsa Bands & Cuban BandsMariachi BandsSteel BandsBagpipersAsian Wedding EntertainmentMedieval Musicians & MinstrelsUnique & Unusual MusiciansToastmastersMotivational SpeakersMagiciansCaricaturistsMix and Mingle EntertainmentWedding EntertainersAcrobatsAerialistsBalloon ModellersChildrens EntertainersChristmas EntertainersComediansCostume CharactersCircus ActsDancersFace PaintersFire PerformersJugglersLiving StatuesLiving TablesLookalikesPaparazzi PhotographersStilt WalkersStreet PerformersWedding DJsParty DJsMobile DiscosNorthern Soul DJsPhoto BoothsSelfie MirrorsEvent DecorEvent SuppliersFairground RidesFood & Drink SuppliersFunfair StallsGiant and Outdoor GamesLight Up LettersMixologist Cocktail BartendersMobile BarsMobile Casinos
Event Type
Your event type...WeddingCivil PartnershipCorporate EventPrivate PartyBar Mitzvah / Bat MitzvahCharity EventHotel / Restaurant EventVenue / Pub / Club EventFestival / Outdoor EventUniversity EventHM Forces / Army / Navy / RAF EventOther Event TypeHoliday Camp / Cruise ShipExhibition / Trade FairRegatta / Sporting EventFuneral
Event Location & Date
Your event location...BerkshireBuckinghamshireEast SussexEssexHampshireKentLondonOxfordshireSurreyWest SussexBristolCornwallDevonDorsetGloucestershireSomersetWiltshireHerefordshireShropshireStaffordshireWarwickshireWest MidlandsWorcestershireDerbyshireLeicestershireLincolnshireNorthamptonshireNottinghamshireBedfordshireCambridgeshireHertfordshireNorfolkSuffolkCheshireCumbriaGreater ManchesterLancashireMerseysideDurhamNewcastle upon TyneNorthumberlandEast YorkshireNorth YorkshireSouth YorkshireWest YorkshireAngleseyBlaenau GwentBridgendCaerphillyCardiffCarmarthenshireCeredigionConwyDenbighshireFlintshireGwyneddMerionethMonmouthshireNeath Port TalbotNewportPembrokeshirePowysRadnorRhondda Cynon TafSwanseaTorfaenTydfilWrexhamAberdeenAberdeenshireAngusArgyll and ButeClackmannanshireDumfriesshireDundeeEast AyrshireEast DunbartonshireEast LothianEast RenfrewshireEdinburghFalkirkFifeGlasgowHighlandInverclydeMidlothianMorayNa h-Eileanan an IarNorth AyrshireOrkney IslandsPerth and KinrossRenfrewshireScottish BordersShetland IslandsSouth AyrshireStirlingWest DunbartonshireWest LothianAntrimArmaghBelfastDownFermanaghLondonderryTyroneCarlowCavanClareCorkDonegalDublinGalwayKerryKildareKilkennyLaoisLeitrimLimerickLongfordLouthMayoMeathMonaghanOffalyRoscommonSligoTipperaryWaterfordWestmeathWexfordWicklowAll foreign locations
Call us now on 01782 740839
Home
Browse Artists Artists
Weddings Weddings
Corporate Corporate
Parties Parties
Other Events Other Events
Inspiration Inspiration
Privacy Policy
At Alive Network, we are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy.
Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to enquiries@alivenetwork.com or by writing to Alive Network Limited, Silk Mill Studios, Princess Street, Newcastle under Lyme, Staffordshire ST5 1DD. Alternatively, you can telephone 01782 740839.
Who are we?
We're Alive Network, the UK's largest live entertainment booking agency. Alive Network is a registered limited company (Registered Company Number: 04084200). Our registered offices are Ground Floor Suite, Silk Mill Studios, Princess Street, Newcastle-under-Lyme, Staffordshire, ST5 1DD, United Kingdom
How do we collect information from you?
We obtain information about you when you use our website, submit an enquiry via the website, phone or email.
What information do we collect?
We collect the following information:
Name (and business name if applicable)
Contact information including address, phone, email and IP address
Demographic information such as postcode, event address
Credit card details
Bank details
Other information relevant to your enquiry
What do we do with the information we gather?
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
If you have booked entertainment through Alive Network Limited, your event details and personal information will be passed to the performer(s) you have booked. This is solely for the performer to contact you regarding your event and will not be used for marketing purposes privately by the performer.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about artists or services which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided, but only if you have made an enquiry with us, and only if you have not opted out of receiving promotional emails.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity. When you have entered into a contract with us, we will hold you data securely for 6 years to help support our financial reporting requirement.
Who has access to your information?
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
We use a third-paty email marketing company, SendGrid, to deliver all mail from Alive Network. This includes both transactional and marketing emails. We gather information regarding delivery success and open rates to ensure our customers receive our emails and to help us improve future marketing. You can read SendGrid's privacy policy here
Website recording
Our web site may also use HotJar heatmap and visitor recording software. Hotjar may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling and any text keyed into website forms. The information collected does not include bank details or any sensitive personal data. Data collected by Hotjar is for Alive Network's internal use only. The information collected is used to improve our website usability and is stored and used for aggregated and statistical reporting.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
If you would like to remove your personal details from our website, please contact admin@alivenetwork.com or login to your account and click the "remove personal information" button in your profile.
A UK-wide & International Entertainment AgencyWe book acts for venues across the UK and internationally.
South East London BerkshireBrightonBuckinghamshireCanterburyChichesterEast SussexEssexHampshireHoveKentOxfordOxfordshirePortsmouthSouthamptonSurreyWest SussexWinchester
South West BathBristolCornwallDevonDorsetExeterGloucesterGloucestershirePlymouthSalisburySomersetTruroWellsWiltshire
North West CarlisleCheshireChesterCumbriaGreater ManchesterLancashireLancasterLiverpoolManchesterMerseysidePrestonSalford
North East DurhamNewcastle upon TyneNorthumberland West Midlands HerefordHerefordshireLichfieldShropshireStaffordshireStoke-on-TrentWarwickshireWest MidlandsWorcesterWorcestershire
East Midlands DerbyDerbyshireLeicesterLeicestershireLincolnLincolnshireNorthamptonshireNottinghamNottinghamshire
East of England BedfordshireCambridgeCambridgeshireChelmsfordElyHertfordshireNorfolkNorwichPeterboroughSt AlbansSuffolk
Yorkshire and the Humber BradfordEast YorkshireLeedsNorth YorkshireRiponSheffieldSouth YorkshireWakefieldWest YorkshireYork
Wales Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Cardiff
Carmarthenshire Ceredigion
Conwy Denbighshire
Flintshire
Gwynedd
Monmouthshire
Neath Port Talbot
Newport Pembrokeshire
Powys Rhondda Cynon Taf Swansea
Torfaen
Wrexham
Scotland Aberdeen Aberdeenshire Angus Argyll and Bute Clackmannanshire Dumfriesshire Dundee East Ayrshire East Dunbartonshire East Lothian East Renfrewshire Falkirk Highland Inverclyde Midlothian Moray Na h-Eileanan an Iar North Ayrshire North LanarkshireOrkney Islands
Perth and Kinross Renfrewshire Scottish Borders Shetland Islands South Ayrshire South Lanarkshire Stirling West Dunbartonshire West LothianNorthern Ireland Antrim Armagh Belfast Down Fermanagh Londonderry Tyrone Republic of Ireland
We believe in making events extraordinary
Check out a small selection of the clients we've impressed with our hand-picked rosters of amazing artists!
Over
1
4
3
2
8
6
events since 1999
Over 143286 Events Since 1999
5000+ Hand Picked Artists
24-Hour Emergency Cover
Alive Network Ltd
Silk Mill Studios, Princess StreetNewcastle-under-Lyme, Staffordshire, ST5 1DDENGLAND
Get Directions
Customer service Customer service Customer service
Your Basket Your Wishlist Your Customer Account Contact Alive Network Frequently Asked Questions Advice Articles & Entertainment Ideas Terms and Conditions Privacy policy
Find what you're looking for Find what you're looking for Find what you're looking for
Live Bands for Hire Hand-Picked Artist Collections Wedding Music & Entertainment Corporate Entertainment Party Entertainment Charity Event Entertainment Pub, Club & Venue Entertainment Hotel & Restaurant Entertainment
About Us About Us About Us
About Alive Network Join Alive Network (Artists) Artist Account Sign-In Artist Management & Development Our Recording Studio Artist Production Services Job opportunities at Alive An Award Winning Employer
Explore Alive Explore Alive Explore Alive
Customer Review Centre Our Facebook Page Our Twitter Feed Our YouTube Channel Our Pinterest Boards Our LinkedIn Page Guide to Booking Function Bands How To Book A Band Links To Our Friends & Partners
Registered offices: Ground Floor Suite, Silk Mill Studios, Princess Street, Newcastle-under-Lyme, Staffordshire, ST5 1DD, United KingdomAll content © Copyright Alive Network 1999-2020. All rights reserved. Registered Company Number: 04084200Some artists may appear with the kind co-operation and consent of their respective management companies.This service is intended for personal use only and no part of the service may be displayed in public, broadcast or used for any business purpose without the consent of Alive Network. Whilst every effort is made to ensure the accuracy of our services and web content, we accept no responsibility for any use made of the information provided and we shall not be liable for any loss suffered thereby.
© Copyright Alive Network 1999-2020
